bislr.com 2019-12-30

# Autopilot Privacy Policy: visual marketing automation software

AutopilotHQ, Inc. (“Autopilot,” “we” or “us”) makes available certain online tools, including its Autopilot services, comprised of certain “software as a service” offerings that include tools, content and resources that allow you to automate your sales and marketing processes.

This Privacy Policy applies to www.autopilothq.com (the “Site”) which is owned and operated by Autopilot, as well as to the Autopilot software and services provided by Autopilot (the “Services”). At Autopilot, we recognize and respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and disclose personally identifying information about individuals (“Personal Information”) that is gathered through our Site and Services.

By using our Site and Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy, which is subject to and incorporates by reference our Terms of Use, including their limitation on liability. To review the Terms of Use, go to terms of use.

In this Policy, the following definitions apply:

  * The term “Customer” means a customer of Autopilot who is a user of the Site and a subscriber of the Services.
  * The term “Consumer” means a customer or user of a website developed and operated by an Autopilot Customer.
  * We may collect certain Personal Information from our Customers. Through the provision of our Services, we may also receive information, which may include Personal Information, about Consumers who use our Customers’ Sites. This Privacy Policy applies to how Autopilot uses and discloses the Personal Information it collects or receives through the Site or Service.
  * This Privacy Policy does not apply (i) to the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information about Consumers by our Customers, or (ii) to our Customers’ websites. We have no control over our Customer’s information privacy practices. You should check the Privacy Policy of any website you use for information about how that site collects, uses and discloses Personal Information.

## Changes to this privacy policy

As we update our Site and Services and roll-out new versions or features, we may change this Privacy Policy. You should check http://www.autopilothq.com/legal/privacy-policy frequently to review our current Privacy Policy, which is effective as of the effective date listed above. Your continued use of any of our Site and Services once you have been notified of the modified Privacy Policy constitutes your deemed acceptance and understanding of the Privacy Policy as in effect at the time of your continued use.

## Personal information we collect and receive

### About our customers

Account Information. Customers may browse our Site without creating an online account, but to use our Services you must create an account. To create an account, you must enter your full first and last name, business name and email address.

Payment Information. When you subscribe to our Services, we collect your billing address, credit/debit card number, expiration date, and other billing information necessary to process the transaction. We use this information to process your transaction.

History and Usage. We also collect information about our Customers’ use of the Services, including their order history, Services usage and other similar information.

Facebook. We allow Customers to “Like” our Site and Services through their Facebook Account. However, while we do track which Customers choose to “Like” us, at this time we do not collect any information from Facebook about Customers who choose to “Like” us.

Other Information. In addition, we may ask Customers to submit certain optional information about their business, such as their industry, target customers or demographics, and other information. We may also collect or receive information from third parties (e.g. Slack.com), and public records and sources. We may combine such information with the Personal Information we have collected about Customers.

### About Visitors to our Site

We automatically collect through our Site and Services, information that is often not personally identifiable, such as the website from which visitors came to our Site, IP address, browser type, domain name, referring URL, page views and information relating to the device through which users access the Site. We may combine this information with the Personal Information we have collected about Customers.

### About Consumers

While we do not directly collect any Personal Information from Consumers or users of our Customers’ websites, we may collect certain non-personally-identifiable information about Consumers that use our Customers’ websites, in order to provide Customers with information about how their sites are accessed and used. For example, we may receive IP address, browser type, domain name, referring URL, page views and information relating to the device through which Consumers access our Customers’ Site.

In addition, our Customers may, through their Sites and their use of our Services, collect additional information from Consumers such as name, e-mail address and other contact information. We may receive this Consumer information, which may include Personal Information, and store it on behalf of our Customers. However, we will not use this Personal Information about Consumers for our own purposes. We maintain such Personal Information about Consumers only on behalf of our Customers; this information belongs to our respective Customers, not to Autopilot. As noted above, our Customers’ collection, use and disclosure of Consumer Personal Information is not governed by this Privacy Policy. By disclosing Consumer personal information to Autopilot, a Customer acknowledges that it has read, understood and agreed to this Privacy Policy and warrants that it has obtained the consent of the relevant Consumer to such collection, use and disclosure of personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## How we use personal information

We use the Personal Information we collect online for the following types of purposes:

  * to provide our products and Services to Customers, including to generate reports for Customers about visitors to their Sites;
  * to process payments and orders;
  * to respond to requests or inquiries from Customers, to communicate with Customers about their accounts or orders, and for similar customer-service-related purposes;
  * to effectuate or enforce a transaction or agreement with a Customer;
  * to tailor the information we send or display to Customers;
  * to send marketing and promotional e-mails to our Customers (not Consumers); and
  * to improve our Site, offerings or services and to better understand how users access and use our Site and offerings, on an aggregated and individualized basis.

Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy, we also may use aggregate or non-personally identifying information about Customers or Consumers for market analysis, research, marketing or other purposes. We may also identify your company name and/or logo on client lists, marketing materials, and/or press releases. If you wish to be excluded from this program, do so by emailing: “marketing AT autopilothq.com”.

## How we disclose personal information

We may disclose any of the Personal Information we collect or receive through our Site and Services as follows:

  * to our contractors or service providers who provide services or perform functions on our behalf;
  * in response to a subpoena or other legal process by a governmental entity or third party, or if otherwise required by law;
  * to protect or enforce our rights or property, including as evidence in litigation in which we are involved;
  * in the event of the sale or dissolution (bankruptcy) of assets, in whole or in part, of Autopilot or any of its affiliates; and
  * to our affiliates and subsidiaries, for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Further, we may disclose Consumer information to the Customer who owns such information. As noted above, Consumer information, including Personal Information, belongs to the Customer that operates the website through which the information was collected, not to Autopilot. Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy, our Customers may access, view and download any Consumer information belonging to them, and we have no control over their collection, use or disclosure of this information.

We will not disclose Personal Information to any third parties for such third parties’ own marketing purposes, unless we first receive your consent. However, we may share aggregate or non-personally identifying information with third parties for marketing, advertising, research or other purposes.

## Cookies and analytics

When you interact with our Site, we strive to make your experience easy and meaningful. We or our third party service providers may use cookies, web beacons (clear GIFs, web bugs) and similar technologies to track site visitor activity and collect site data. We may combine this data with the Personal Information we have collected from Customers. In addition, we use cookies to collect site activity data about visitors to our Customers’ sites.

Cookies. We (or our third party service providers) use cookies to track visitor activity on the Site. A cookie is a text file that a website transfers to your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Our cookies assign a random, unique number to each visitor’s computer. They do not contain information that would personally identify the visitor, although we can associate a cookie with any identifying information that is or has been provided by a Customer while visiting our Site. We or our third party service providers use cookies that remain on your computer for a specified period of time or until they are deleted (persistent cookies). These cookies record clickstream information (data reporting the URLs, or names of the pages, on our Site that have been visited). We may also use cookies that exist only temporarily during an online session (session cookies). These cookies allow you to log in to your account and they allow us to identify you temporarily as you move through the Site. Most browsers allow users to refuse cookies, but doing so may impede the functionality of some portions of our Site.

Web Beacons. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, that are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, Web beacons are embedded invisibly on webpages and may not be disabled or controlled through your browser.

Third Parties. As noted, we may also engage third parties to track and analyze site activity on our behalf. To do so, these third parties may place cookies or web beacons to track user activity on our Site. We use the data collected by such third parties to help us administer and improve the quality of the Site and to analyze usage of the Site.

## Third-party links

At times, our Site may contain links to other, third-party websites. Any access to and use of such linked websites is not governed by this Privacy Policy, but, instead, is governed by the privacy policies of those third party websites. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third party websites.

## Customer websites and content

We have no control over, nor are we responsible for, the content of our Customers’ websites. We exercise no editorial or managerial control over Customers’ websites. You should check the Privacy Policy for such website, to understand how your information may be collected, used, disclosed and secured by the operator of such website.

## Marketing communications

To Our Customers. You may opt-in to receive emails from us about information that we believe may be of interest to you as well as news and offers from us or other third parties, which may include our newsletter or information about special offers, products or offerings, or other items.

If, at any time, you would like to stop receiving these promotional e-mails, you may follow the opt-out instructions contained in any such e-mail. If you opt-out of receiving emails or promotions from us, we still may send you e-mail about your account, any Services you have requested or received from us, or for other customer-service purposes.

We will not send emails to Consumers or users of our Customers’ websites. However, our Customers may use Autopilot’s Service to send commercial e-mails to users or Consumers. Under our policies, Customers may only use the Service to send commercial emails to users or Consumers who have opted in to receiving such e-mails. Each email sent by a Customer through our Service contains an opt-out mechanism through which you may tell a Customer you do not wish to receive future marketing emails from the Customer. However, we are not responsible for the emails sent by our Customers, through our Services, and we cannot guarantee that Consumers will follow our policies or comply with applicable laws. Consumers can report suspected abuse to privacy@autopilothq.com.

## Consent to transfer information to the United States and Australia

Please note that information we collect or receive may be transferred to and processed in the United States and in Australia. By using our Site and Services, you consent to the transfer and processing of your Personal Information in the United States and Australia, jurisdictions which may not provide the same level of protection that exists in other countries such as those in the European Economic Area. Your consent is voluntary. If, however, you do not consent, we will not be able to provide you with our Services.

## Security

We use commercially reasonable physical, technical and administrative measures to protect the security of the Personal Information that we collect or receive from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security all of the time.

## EU - U.S. and Swiss - U.S. Privacy Shield

With respect to the Personal Information we receive from or on behalf of our customers in the EU and Switzerland, AutopilotHQ, Inc. in the U.S. complies with the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks, as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. You can review our Privacy Shield Notice at https://www.autopilothq.com/legal/privacy-shield

## Access to personal information

In most circumstances Autopilot allows Customers to access the personal information Autopilot holds about them. However, access may be denied where Autopilot is permitted or required by law to deny access to such information.

Questions? You may contact us with any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy at [privacy@autopilothq.com](mailto:privacy@autopilothq.com).
